https://www.pooldawg.com/article/privacy-policy-terms-of-use/

Cues By Brand
Pool Cues (View All Brands)
Pool Cue Cases
Pool Cue Cases (View All)
Cue Cases By Brand
Cue Cases (View All Brands)
SHOP SOFT CASES
Action, Predator and More...
Truer Rolls, Consistent Results
NEED NEW CLOTH?
NEW TRAINING TOOLS
Get That Winning Edge!
Interested in learning more about improving your game? Visit the PoolDawg Academy >>
Clearance Billiards Supplies
Pool CuesView All Pool CuesCues By StyleView All Cues By StyleLifetime Warranty CuesCarbon Fiber CuesLow Deflection CuesBreak & Break Jump CuesBeginner Pool CuesWomen's Pool CuesSneaky Pete Pool CuesLow Deflection ShaftsTraditional Pool CuesModern CuesFiberglass Bonded CuesOne Piece House CuesSports Team CuesGraphite Pool CuesLimited Edition CuesChildren's CuesSnooker CuesPool Cue ShaftsJump & Masse CuesCustom Pool CuesCarbon Fiber Specialty CuesPool Cue CasesView All Pool Cue CasesCue Cases by SizeView All Cue Cases by Size1 x 1 Cases1 x 2 Cases2 x 2 Cases2 x 4 Cases 3 x 5 Cases3 x 6 Cases3 x 7 Cases4 x 8 CasesCue Cases by StyleView All Cue Cases by StyleHard Pool Cue CasesSoft Pool Cue CasesLeather Pool Cue CasesBox Pool Cue CasesPool Cue AccessoriesView All Pool Cue AccessoriesPool Cue PartsView All Pool Cue PartsPool Cue TipsPool Cue Weight BoltsPool Cue BumpersPool Cue FerrulesJoint ProtectorsPool Cue MaintenanceView All Pool Cue MaintenancePool Cue Tip ToolsPool Cue Shaft ProductsPool Cue Repair ToolsPool Cue ChalkPool Cue ChalkersMore Cue AccessoriesView All More Cue AccessoriesPool and Billiards GlovesPool Cue HoldersBilliards Key ChainsMisc. Billiards AccessoriesPool Cue ExtensionsPool Table AccessoriesView All Pool Table AccessoriesStandard Pool Table AccessoriesView All Standard Pool Table AccessoriesPool Table CoversPool Ball RacksPool Table BrushesPocket MarkersLicensed Pool Table CoversBridge Sticks & BridgesPool and Billiard BallsView All Pool and Billiard BallsBilliards Pool Ball SetsLicensed Pool Ball SetsCue BallsTraining BallsReplacement Pool BallsBilliards Ball StoragePool Ball Cleaning ToolsPool Table Repair and MaintenanceView All Pool Table Repair and MaintenancePool Table PartsPool Table Installation and CleanersPool Table Felt and ClothPool Table PocketsBilliards InstructionView All Billiards InstructionInstructional BooksInstructional DVDsTraining ToolsPoolDawg Academy (Free Articles)Game RoomView All Game RoomFurnishings and Cue RacksView All Furnishings and Cue RacksPool Table LightsFloor RacksBar Stools and ChairsWall RacksGameroom AccessoriesWall Art and PostersPub TablesClocksOther Game Room SuppliesView All Other Game Room SuppliesPing PongShuffleboardGame TablesPool TablesPoker SuppliesDVDs and EntertainmentDarts and Dart BoardsView All Darts and Dart BoardsDart BoardsSteel Tip DartsDart Board CabinetsComplete Dart Board SetsSoft Tip DartsDart AccessoriesBilliards ApparelView All Billiards ApparelPoolDawg ApparelHustlin USA ApparelEight Ball Mafia ApparelClearanceView All ClearanceCertified Preowned Pool Cues (Use code BF-DAWG for EXTRA 10% off)Clearance Billiards Supplies (Use code BF-DAWG for EXTRA 10% off)Certified Preowned Pool Cue Shafts (Use code BF-DAWG for EXTRA 10% off)Certified Preowned Pool Cue Cases (Use code BF-DAWG for EXTRA 10% off)
Search:
My Account
My Wishlist
My Cart
Checkout
Register
Log In
home >
Privacy policy terms of use
Privacy Policy & Terms of Use
Our Commitment to Privacy
Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.
Privacy Policy Statement
This is the web site of The Billiard Exchange dba PoolDawg.com, Inc..
Our postal address is
PO Box 552
Lafayette, CO 80026
We can be reached via e-mail at info@pooldawg.com or you can reach us by telephone at 866-843-3294
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).
We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).
When you visit PoolDawg you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our web site.
If you choose to purchase products or services from Pool Dawg, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:
Name
Mailing address
Email address
Credit card number
Home and business phone number
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, , disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting the Website.
The information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with other marketers to bring you offers of interest. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with other marketers, please email us at info@pooldawg.com or call us at 866-843-3294.
With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart.
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address, writing to us at the above address.
Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.
Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them .
Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address, write to us at the above address, writing to us at the above address.
Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site, We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
Pricing
PoolDawg obtains certain data directly from the manufacturer, publisher or supplier of Products and is not responsible for pricing, typographical or other errors in any such data. In addition, availability of third-party Product is subject to change without notice. PoolDawg reserves the right to cancel orders related to such errors or product discontinuation or unavailability, and to correct this web site at any time, including pricing errors not detected until after PoolDawg's confirmation or e-mail response.
Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?
We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.
What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org, state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau.
Your Credit Card Protects You
Your credit card offers online fraud protection click here for more information.
Discover Click Here
Mastercard Click Here
Visa Click Here
AMEX Click Here
Pooldawg Deals
Sign Up with Your Email for Free Training Articles and Deals
Go
Free Shipping on orders over $99*
60-Day Easy Returns Satisfaction Guaranteed
In-House Experts Pool Players on Staff
HERE'S SOME INFO YOU MAY NEED:
POOLDAWG SERVICES
Get a Free Catalog
Gift Certificates
Customer Service
60 Day 100% Satisfaction Guarantee
Shipping Information
Reviews
PoolDawg Academy - Billiard Training Articles
10 Pool Player Tips for COVID Safety
Advanced Pattern Play: Strategies to RUN OUT More Racks!
Beginner's Guide to Buying a Pool Cue
POOLDAWG BLOG
BLACK FRIDAY WEEK SPECIALS ARE HERE!
PoolDawg's Advanced Instructional Series Staring Florian "Venom" Kohler
Check Out the "Super Hot" Video Preview + MEET Florian "Venom" Kohler Today!
POOLDAWG INFO
866-THE-DAWG (866-843-3294)
PoolDawg Team
About PoolDawg
Contact Us
PoolDawg - The Pool Player's Best Friend
With over 3,000 pool cues, pool cue cases and billiards accessories, it's no wonder that PoolDawg is the pool player's best friend.
As an authorized retailer of 50+ leading brands of pool cues and cue cases, PoolDawg is the ultimate billiards destination for safe, secure, guaranteed shopping. We've helped over 100,000 pool and billiards players find the perfect pool cues and billiards accessories just for their game. Our staff is filled with people who actually play pool and our mission is to make sure that every one of our customers find the gear that will help take their game to the next level.
PoolDawg - Loyally Serving Pool Players Since 2003.
© 2020 The Billiard Exchange dba PoolDawg.com, IncPrivacy Policy & Terms of UseSite MapContact Us
